Oh!
Oh! Oh!
of
the
game is playing.
Give me the three titles and
my children to be convinced.
Let me know the ones who
are playing together.
This is Akiba Maid War
Welcome to Akiba Maid War,
a Japanese anime character,
a Japanese character.
Welcome to Akiba Maid War,
a Japanese anime character.
Thank you so much
for
joining us.
Why?
Hey, I'm made way.
B감 minstress.
I'm using a Georgia.
I'm gonna burn burn burn!
I'm amazing. Take
a
look
over there.
It's Oinkidoink. What about him?
I hear Ronko Menon just
joined their group.
Huh?
The one who got busted 15 years ago?
She's back working in Akiba? She is.
And as a novice maid.
They've been going around crushing
places ever since she joined.
So we have ourselves a new war pig, huh?
We're all created creatures!
Listen up!
Tell me, what is the
Creatureland Group's purpose?
To unify the Keeper Boss!
The following three cafes get up here.
Foxy Vixen Cafe. Yes, sir!
Devoted Maid Dog Cafe. Yes, sir!
Oinky Doink Cafe.
There are three great attributes
every maid in our group should have.
One is the ability to fight.
Oh, thanks, madam.
Another is the ability to make money.
Thank you, I'm honored.
And then, the most important attribute.
Why?
Did you think we wouldn't notice?
You're embezzling from the group.
Allow me to take the fall for this, madam.
The most important attribute to have
is, of course.
loyalty toward the Creatureland group.
In order to enforce these attributes, we
will be sending Drillmasters to each cafe.
All right, Sows, do any of you
know what this cafe is missing?
Cool vibes, some
craftiness, kindness, maybe?
Steadfast resolve, the chief
capable of running a kiffy.
No, Swine, it's our lack
of maid-like activities.
Huh?
The chief is so right.
I've hardly done anything
maid-like since I've come to Akiba.
The group is sending us a Drillmaster
to straighten our asses up.
For real? Huh? Huh?
What's a Drill Master?
They're specialists in teaching
maids how to properly run a cafe.
Rumors are, most maids get crushed
under their hellish training.
They...
they get crushed?
Once the Drill Master's here,
we're gonna try real hard!
We always try real hard, Chief.
Welcome home to the pigsty, mistress!
There is somewhere!
Your masters are supposed to
want to come home to a pigsty?
Uh, well...
Well, this is just part of our cafe theme.
It's a maid cafe, but it's
also a pigsty. Ludicrous.
Huh? Luda what? Oink?
I'm the dispatch from the group Sano.
Every single one of you fails.
The place is dirty, the
decorations are half-assed,
you are all over-reliant
on your star employee,
and even she gets away with stale service.
The rest of you are so empty-headed
you only know how to snort.
Above all, you have no
loyalty towards the group.
You're the sorriest maids I've ever seen.
Now go re-educate all useless maids.
Yes, Madam Creature!
Cut off any maids you come
across and deem too hopeless.
Yes, Madam Creature!
I accept no failures in
training our creatures.
Your life depends on this.
Yes, Madam Creature!
Your training starts tomorrow morning.
If you pass the test within a week,
I'll report to the higher-ups that
you're not a problem and need not be cut.
A test?
You each will be required to
squeeze out at least 100,000.
You hear that, piglets?
The benevolent Miss Sano is giving
you one last and final chance.
So get your heads in the game.
You. Yes, madam.
The group is cutting you off.
The panda two.
Uh, wait, why is that?
You two are a bad influence on the maids.
They are undisciplined.
You're rotten apples.
No, more like sickly pigs.
Oh, but no, I'm a very healthy piggy boo.
I'm saying this out of kindness.
Or would you rather Creatureland
disown you completely?
Anything but that.
Please leave. Yes, madam.
Not our chief.
Starting today and onwards, you will treat
me as if I am the Creatureland group.
Reveille is at 5 a .m. That is all.
Nogomi, it's time to get up. What's that?
Aw, come on, I'm not that adorable.
Excuse me for this.
It's time to get up.
Okay, I'm awake.
Welcome home, my mistress.
What?
Louder.
Welcome home, my mistress. I said louder.
Totally out of sync.
Now do it again! Right!
Answer yes, Madam Creature.
Yes, Madam Creature!
I'm all done drawing, Madam.
What the hell is this?
Uh, a kitty cat?
Do it again.
What a waste!
If you think so, then draw it properly.
Think of that poor sweet omelet.
Welcome home!
One oinky-doink drink combo.
Thanks, oinky-doink!
You. Yes, ma 'am?
Is your head full of pig slop?
That much syrup can't possibly be
any good for the master's health.
I'm saying dilute it with more water.
But with the right amount
based on cost, we...
Is that all you care about?
Money, money, money.
Go ahead and comment on
each other's weaknesses.
You can't think of any because
you pigs can't think at all.
Then let me start for you. Shipon.
What's with that makeup?
It's not appropriate for the
Creatureland group. What?
Can we at least wear makeup the way we...
Ah, bitch!
This maid cafe is part of
the Creatureland group.
Unless you change your whole appearance,
you won't be passing my test.
I'm so sleepy.
I think that there's more stuff.
What's that?
I expect you sows to make a
carving of this in a week.
What does that have to
do with being a maid?
Ouch!
Get carving, or you'll
get even less sleep.
May I turn out the lights
so we can go to sleep?
Ronko, do you think being a maid is
about working for her parent group?
That's also an important factor.
Good night.
So very hungry.
Oh hey!
I've got some bamboo leaves.
Want to eat them?
Of course.
You don't want them.
You're human, after all.
Do you realize it's morning?
Assembly time.
Yeah, we're boycotting that today.
So you want to leave?
The Creature Land Group.
We just want a different drill master.
We don't think it's efficient to be
trained by someone we don't agree with.
I've been given full
authority on this matter.
You're not the boss of us.
Boycott.
Please put that away.
So I see it was all done
for your own betterment.
But I suppose I must have
taken the wrong approach.
I apologize.
What's up with this change in attitude?
Let me talk to you
individually before I go.
If you still decide to kick me
out after that, I will comply.
What do you think? Whatever.
I guess we can at least listen?
Uh, I wonder what she wants to talk about.
Nagomi, take a good look at the
Creatureland group building.
What do you think?
Um, it's really big.
do you know what the
relationship is between the
group and its maids uh
no not really I see them
Don't worry.
I swear on my life I won't
let go of you. No! Move me up!
Our arms represent the relationship
between the group and its maids.
Do you understand?
Yes, yes, I do understand.
That's not how you answer.
Yes, yes, yes, Madam Creature!
Madam Creature!
Look at this. Oink! Do you see?
Yes, yes.
Tell me what it is you see.
I'm sorry, I don't understand.
This arm represents the group.
It protects its maids no
matter how much it gets hurt.
In return, maids squeeze out
their honey money for the group.
That's the kind of supportive
relationship we share together.
Right! Of course, madam!
Of course it is!
She threw me off the damn building what
the heck man that's total crap right.
Huh what the fuck dudes
you know i admit the stuff
miss sano tells us it's
actually pretty decent
huh maybe she's not such
a bad person after all
and i would like to see
what i can learn from
her teachings the hell
but we're gonna kick her
out right guys what if
we see how things go it
might not be that bad
really what about you
ronko i believe it might
be worth the experience.
Wait are y 'all for real
smells so good oh the
crunchy part of the
chicken rice is in here.
We're totally scoring
welcome home welcome home
allow us to see you all
allow us to see you all.
What's your work attitude
going to be for today?
We work with gratitude for our group!
Yumechi! Yes! Yumechi! Yes! Yumechi! Yes!
Yumechi!
Yes! Yumechi! Yes!
Good job squeezing out
the 100,000 for the group!
Thank you, madam!
You have anything to say?
I am glad to have contributed
to the Creatureland group!
Don't get complacent!
Aren't you the star?
You can squeeze out a lot more then!
With pleasure!
Good!
Now all of you go and serve
your little pig asses off!
Yes, Madam Creature!
Anyone else? Yes!
Okay, Zoya!
Nagomi wasn't insistent enough and her
master left without ordering anything.
Zoya, thank you so much
for your great comment!
Instructor Sano, please do your worst!
Ready, Madam Creature?
Thank you so very much!
Anyone else?
Huh? What?
Shippon played hooky again.
She missed today's practice.
Instructor Sano, I don't feel any
loyalty toward the group from her at all.
But you guys...
Sweet! Sweet! Sweet!
Don't you feel better?
Do you now see the joy in working
for that sweet honey money?
Tomorrow we start doing our
best for the sake of the group.
Instructor Sano, thank you very much.
What are you doing?
A deserter!
Get her!
Oh, man!
Woo-hoo, sheep-on.
Come out, come out, wherever you are.
It's okay.
Everyone makes mistakes
now and then
you
can
leave
through here what so you're
gonna let me go if that is what
you want what about you are
you going to stay and be a
maid all I care about is
making sure I protect this cafe
what about you I don't know
I just kind of fell into
the business I've never stuck
with other jobs in the past
like this one so why was
being a maid the one thing I
kept doing I get it I had a
lot of fun just being a maid.
There you go.
Thanks, Ronko.
I wonder what else is out there.
This isn't the oinky-doink I know anymore.
Huh?
Oh, hey.
Ronko, on second thought,
I still want to be a maid.
Who's that?
She's so cute.
Starting today, I'll work my heart
out for the sake of the group.
You look much cuter that way.
It suits you well.
Thank you very much.
Now focus!
Time for assembly!
Yes, Madam Creature!
Here's the hundred thousand
I made, Instructor?
You sure made me wait!
Yes, Madam Creature.
Time to announce the final
results of your maid training.
Right!
You're the sorriest bunch
of maids I've ever seen.
Right!
Your heads are full of slop, your dues
are overdue, and you always avoid work.
That's the kind of
despicable maids you are.
Right!
And yet, you are the best.
Every one of you passes.
Right!
Maids don't cry that easily.
We're not crying.
Listen up!
From now on,
look at the result of
your teamwork to remind
yourselves that you are maids
in the Creatureland group!
Yes, Santa Creature!
Thank you so much!
Thank you so very much, Instructor Sano!
Oh, Kachimachi.
You're tired, aren't you?
I am, too.
I'm so very sleepy for some reason.
I'm so sleepy.
But, you know, did I
really do anything wrong?
I always get my ass yelled at because
they never earn enough money for me to...
Now I'm getting pissed off!
Time for you sickly pigs to come back.
Please, master.
I don't want to lose to
Yumechi and have her rub
it in my face that she's
a better pig than me.
Okay, what is it you want?
Order a song for me and
I'll squeal for you.
Hey, Zoya, where's Shippan?
I think she went for a
stroll a little while ago.
Yumechi, your face doesn't
look too good, you okay?
No, I feel fine.
I just need to keep
working on cutting costs
to earn enough honey
money to pay her dues.
You pig dicks!
This shit ends right now! Uh-uh. Chief?
And Sheepon?
The oinky-doink belongs to me!
I'll make you regret that
you kicked me out on my ass!
Hey, where do you think you're going?
Here!
You need to stop right there!
I don't think so.
Bronco, what are you doing? Now go.
Thanks, Bronco!
Out of the out of your fucking mind.
Nogomi, stop her! I'm on it!
Shiba, no!
Put that down!
Don't!
Anything but that!
That represents the bond between
us and instructor Soto! I beg you!
Remember what we worked for!
The sake of the group!
I don't fucking care!
This is for the moments
that are actually fun,
even in this smelly-ass pig shit town!
Now listen up, you swine!
Snap out of it and come back!
Why is that damn panda here?
Okachi-machi! Here you go.
Yummy bamboo leaves.
Hey, Chief, you went and ate
a parfait again, didn't you?
Oh, man, busted.
I hid one as hell.
You too, Zoya?
What's happening here?
They're back where they started.
Are you coming or going?
Like, make up your mind already.
What in the world is going on here?
You know that won't do. Mistress,
I'm very sorry, but there are other masters
present, so could you kindly vacate?
Silence!
What did I tell you about
that hideous makeup?
It doesn't look good on you at all!
My makeup's the bomb just the
way it is, thank you very much.
You don't matter anymore.
You've gone too far this time.
We've got some handsome masters
in here, so keep it down, please.
Instructor Sano, you can't go
slapping sheep on like that.
It's no good.
They're all hopeless.
I accept no failures in
training our creatures.
Your life depends on this.
I'm responsible for all of this.
I'll get cut off.
No, disowned even.
Allow us to see you off, mistress.
These strokes. Nice. Stop and flick.
Nagomi. Yes, sir?
You've gotten better at this.
Thank you so very much!
Nogomi Wahira, age 17.
I'm having loads of fun and
learning a lot as a cute maid.
Hey, Shippon!
Being a maid sure is a lot of fun.
You totally got that right.
In your house?
You're finally transitioned!
This bill is based.
Highly intelligent?
Do I see
the sky?
It's the end of the day,
but it's the
end of the day.
It's the end of the day,
and it's the end of the day.